I'm really in trouble. I'm in trouble.
No, I'm fine. When does it start?
Yes.
We've started live distribution, so please give us a hand.
Yes, thank you very much.
Oh, hi!
He didn't show up until the last minute, and this guy showed up about 30 seconds ago.
What was he doing?
I don't know what I was doing.
Well, good evening.
Good evening.
Yesterday and today were beautiful days.
Yes, it was 30 degrees Celsius.
It's a waste of time to stay inside during the daytime, isn't it?
I know.
It's a waste.
I felt like I had to do something.
So I go outside.
I thought, "Yay!" to the sun, and went out.
"Yay!" to the sun.
You mean you took a picture? Thank you.
You mean good job? Like nice.
We did do a "nice sunshine, yay" kind of thing.
You did?
I'm indoors a lot for work.
Well, it's not so easy... so we'll start recording again this week.
So we'll start recording again this week.
I'm sorry, but we're going to start talking about June from now on.
We're going to talk about June at once.
Well, today, too, we've started a cheerful, fun and energetic live broadcast, just like a ship.
Like a ship, we'll be cheerful, happy, and energetic.
And the date is already the 2nd of June!
How fast!
But I feel like it's a long month, because May is until the 31st.
It's full of life, with Golden Week and all.
That's right.
By the way, there are only 30 days in June.
Today is June 2nd.
It's the anniversary of the opening of the Port of Yokohama!
June 2nd is the anniversary of the opening of the Port of Yokohama.
We'll have fireworks at this time, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
By the way, it's also the anniversary of Nagasaki's opening of the school no! What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up!
Excuse me! Let's use it! By the way, I've heard this before.
Why was the port built in Yokohama? Actually, Yokohama is a big city now. It's just a short train ride from Tokyo. But back then, it was a very rural area.
I see.
It was like a Yokohama village.
A village?
Of course, there weren't as many people as there are now. So the Edo shogunate didn't know what they would do if they were too close.
If they came suddenly and said, "Yay, yay, yay, what's going on," we would be afraid.
I was afraid that if they came suddenly and said, "Yay, yay, yay, how are you doing?
I think Yokohama was the perfect place.
So it was between the two.
That's how it happened.
Yokohama.
That's exactly what happened.
And you know what's more, there was another interesting thing.
June 2nd, the day of betrayal.
What?
How scary!
This is the day of betrayal, June 2nd, 1582, Tensho 10, according to the old record.
Oda Nobunaga was betrayed by Akechi Mitsuhide at Honnoji Temple.
Nobunaga Oda was betrayed by Mitsuhide Akechi, and was attacked while he was in Honnoji Temple, and then committed suicide.
The Honnoji area
The Honnoji Incident took place on this very day.
Oh, I see.
That's scary.
What's that?
It's glowing.
It's like... like... like... like... like... like Cirpolo is attacking me.
That's what I meant. That's what I meant.
Did you already have a relationship with him?
Like Mizuhide Akechi.
Like this.
Sha-sha-sha-sha!
Sha-sha-sha!
Sound or don't sound?
Don't make a sound or don't make a sound!
You know, there are so many anniversaries, and the funny thing is...
Today is June 2nd, and tomorrow is Saturday, June 3rd, and... you know, anniversaries... they're so full of them, and the funny thing is...
Today is June 2nd, and tomorrow is Saturday, June 3rd.It's June 2 today and tomorrow, Saturday, June 3.
June 3 also has a very interesting anniversary!
What a clunker day!
Wow, that was very vocal.
That was the loudest voice I've heard all week.
It's Sarpon Day!
Yay!
See you later.
Why the clunk?
There's a music producer who produces a lot of events and live concerts, and he's really famous, but he writes so many misspelled words in his letters and e-mails that everyone calls him a clodhopper... I heard that his birthday is on the 3rd of June.
What's your birthday, by the way? January 20th.
What do we do now? Leave?
Make it the 3rd of June.
It's easy to change your profile!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Betrayal Day.
By the way, "clank" is an old word meaning to hit someone with a bone.
and then the word "clank" came to be used in the same way as "broken" now.
He's a bit of a broken-down radio.
I want him to sing.
I want him to sing to someone far away.
A broken radio.
Well, well, well... it's been a long time coming.
So I'll tell you what...
Before I write to you...
Since tomorrow is the day of the clunkers, I'd like to show you some pictures of the Serpent Army.
I have two pictures, one of this and one of that, but I'll choose the one on the left.
I've got two photos of the Serpentine Army, one on the left and one on the right.
Fanta group, right?
Coke... a bottle... a bottle was always a bottle... a bottle was too much... a yurt...
I don't know... maybe when I was in middle school... they finally came out with cans...
But plastic bottles are a recent thing for me...
What's wrong with this? I've been doing a lot of sauna work.
Sauna activity? It's a sauna kind of place. It's a sauna kind of place.
I went there with members and friends.
After the sauna, I found this Binfanta after I was done with the sauna.
I had never seen it before.
I was quite familiar with bottled cola.
I knew it was there, but I had never seen it before.
So I knew what it was.
I had never had a bottle of Fanta before.
So I tried it.
It's just like a bottle of cola.
I guess it's different from beer, too.
I don't know if cans or bottles are better or worse, but they are.
We drank a lot of beer, and we just kept on drinking.
There is a game called Prospey, Pro Baseball Spirits.
It's called Prosperity Spirits and I play it with my friends.
I know Prosperity Spirits, I know it, I know it, I know it!
And I'm really into it right now.
And we're drinking this together.
That's right.
Doing it?
And then we did this.
This is what we did.
This is what won when myself and my group partner, Shingo, and I fought over communication.
By the way, it's like Sawapon became the Bay Stars.
Shingo became the Dragons.
But isn't it a pretty good game? It was a good game. 7 to 6.
Like this, right? Like this.
Amazing!
It's a great game.
I'm in the midst of a Prosperity boom.
I've got my own team.
I have a very good set up.
I've done it.
I'm listening to what they're saying,
I'm really fulfilled. I'm not saying that.
That's not true.
I'm just having fun at Fanta with my friends. You know...
I'm a sauna.
I feel like I'm really enjoying my life.
But I feel like I'm more youthful now than when I was a student.
On the contrary.
I feel that way.
Well, well, well.
Let's get this out of the way, and then... let's go to the letter.
This one's a little cute.
He's still a teenager, by the way. He's still a teenager, by the way. Oh. I love Ebitu-chan.
I've seen him before.
Oh, by the way, uh, what the heck is this?Er, by the way, er, what the heck.
Hello, drooling master, hungry Mr. Rhea, and super cute little shrimp chow.
Thank you. Thank you.
All right. The meat arrived the other day, so we grilled one piece of meat. Eh, it was just a little nice meat, so we grilled it rare one piece at a time and ate it slowly without dipping it in anything.
Oh no, that's good... that's good...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
One piece at a time.
I love it!
For a young man... a young man... a young man... a 19 year old teenager...
19 years old, teenager...
Yes, yes!
It's big in a big iron plate.
I knew it'd be a waste... right?
No, no, no, one piece at a time. But cook one piece at a time and eat it carefully.
It's good. This is good too.
I wouldn't put any on. Well, well, well, well.
Well, well, well, well, well. I didn't put any on the first slice.
So the ideal thing is to start with a little salt, salt, salt, salt, salt, salt, salt, salt and pepper.
And then you eat it, and then you add the sauce at the very end.
I'm following you.
And, uh... a fun little plant...
It's a plant that has something to do with Ebituramphus.
It's a plant called "koebisou".
I've never seen it before, but Shie Inae, a resident of Tokyo's Shincho Ward, says it looks like a shrimp's tail.
It looks like a shrimp's tail, so people say it looks like a little finger.
Also known as "veloperone-ee-pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero pero   The color! Very shrimpy!
Red and white!
I've never seen it before!
It's a little gross at night!
Yes, it is!
When you look at it, it's pink and pretty.
But at night, it really looks like a shrimp!
It's a combination of a plant and a shrimp!
Only a shrimp!
I didn't know that and I've never seen it before! I've never seen a shrimp before!
Peroperone
I wonder if they say that.
Also, Mr. G2.
Sagamihara City Minami-ku Male
Oh wow genius master Sawapon-san!
I wish I could have an Ebichu soon!
Kombande Bill
Well, I'm from Machida of that server, so Machida has been buzzed about in the program.
I've lived in Minami-ku, Sagamihara City, Asaoku, Kawasaki City, and Midori-ku, Yokohama City, but I've never lived in Machida City!
Oh!
Sawapon-san, Machida is a bit of a wonder, isn't it?
I wanted to ask someone who has lived in Machida
By the way, the people around
My friend doesn't think Machida is Tokyo at all
He just sent me a picture.
Fujino flowers at Yakushiike Park.
Yaguchi Pond Park is also famous.
When the master sang a song about Machida, he took a picture of Yakuchi Pond Park.
I saw the Fujino flower then, too.
Which is it, really? I mean...
Tokyo.
Don't ask the citizens of Machida.
It's a sensitive issue! Yes, it is.
But when I get a car, they say I'm in Tokyo for a moment.
So, I took the car to Machida, and for a moment, I was in Nami, Nami, Nami.
I'm in Kanagawa Prefecture.
It happens a couple of times, doesn't it?
It's complicated, isn't it?
That's right, because of the river and so on.
So, all this time, Machida has been Tokyo.
No, well, because it is, administratively speaking.
Yes, it is. I have been going there with my chest out, but I have been working for TVK.
Lately, I'm starting to think that it would be good to be in Kanagawa.
I want to be in Kanagawa.
From Nakajima's point of view, right?
Yes, that's right. How about in Kanagawa?
I heard that food is very strong in Kanagawa, and it's close by, too.
Then, let's go to Kanagawa.
I'm mad at you all, don't fuck with me! Ha ha ...  but it really touched me... so he drew me a picture of it... uh, are you going to make blue money in Nakahara, Kawasaki City?
It's really good!
I was so impressed by the master's performance that I drew the illustration in the style of "The Wind Rises".
By the way, I asked him to draw those two people, but he said the person next to them is Mariko.
I'd like to declare a winner!
And that's it!
Not this way, this way!Oh, not this way. This way.
Wait a minute. Here we go.
Just a little Ghibli world.
Oh! Cute! Amazing! This is amazing.
I'm so happy. I wish they'd stay like this.
Samorika is so precious.
I love it!
Nice picture. Lovely.
Thank you very much.
And now...
And... we're doing a live broadcast.
Mr. Michiali here... well, let me show you the picture... Mr. Michiali... there was something on the ground... not two plastic bottles... but a blue one.
I wondered what it was... so I was approaching it.
Then, what do you think?
This looks like the earth, doesn't it?
A ball.
And this is actually a ball with an earth pattern.
Like this.
It's a ball?
Isn't it great?
The earth is amazing!
I went up to it and thought, "What the hell is that?
I thought, "Wow, it's the Earth.
And then I picked this up, and I was like, "Wow, he's the guy who rules the Earth.
It's great! It's a dream come true for the kids playing with it.
It's like, "Let's learn the country too." That's great.
It's pretty good, so I should say it's good, but it's not written in English or in katakana.
It says "Indian Ocean" or just "Indian Ocean," which I thought was amazing.
I thought it was amazing.
Why is the earth falling?
They forgot about it. You forgot the earth.
It's amazing that you picked this out of all the balls.
I've never seen it before. Where do you sell it? I'm just curious.
I'd like to see the earth... I'd like to see the earth... I'd like to see the earth... I'd like to throw it in Italy.
It's on May 18th, that's tomorrow, Thursday, at 7:30 p.m.
I'll be doing a show called "Mayamarika's Anime 300%! on Nico Nico Channel at 7:30 p.m. on Thursday, May 18.
And I was invited! I was invited!
I was really surprised!
I was surprised too!
Guest Obayashi on the schedule was a little too funny.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I'm glad to see you're having your usual gung-ho moment.
I think it's not so much that I can accept it, but rather that I want you to talk about it.
I'd like to talk about Gundam stuff. Please join us at 7:30pm.
Nico Nico Channel! Everyone watching the show will be smiling.
It's a channel, isn't it? Yes.
It's a kind of distribution.
Let's go!
I really like your latent photos... and I've been asked to go on a date... with you.
So this week's edition of the Dam Delivery has been just like this.
How about it?
I'm sure there's something here... but I saw a building charge just now...
Thank you... for the bottle of Sarpon's Binfanta.
I'll be sending you a spacha during the first live devils in the building.
I love being in the museum.
I'm the one who should get the Devil's Charge booby prize for 300% of the anime.
I'll just get it when I do it, right?
Chess is that thing... the show before that... is it really an anime?
I was in it before.
I've been allowed to show it before... yes... well, you have to give it 300%... that's what I mean.
You're right, it's all in the quotes.
But if you don't do that, you won't make it to 300?
I'll show you...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's not that bad.
Thank goodness we were born in a better time!
See you later!
Was it something like this?
Was it like this? Well, well, well.
Not yet.